DENNIS VILLAVICENCIO QUINTERO

DEVELOPER | CYBERSECURITY SPECIALIST

630-633-118

dennisvillavicencioq@gmail.com

in

linkedin.com/in/dennis-villavicencioquintero-990180298



github.com/Dennis-Villa

Q

Rafael García Pérez St, 2, 3A, Las Palmas de Gran Canaria. Las Palmas

ABOUT ME

I am a developer and researcher with experience in web and AI application development. I use frameworks and libraries such as NodeJs and ReactJs applying clean architectures and I have a Certificate of Professionalism in Cybersecurity that complements my way of working, which has led me to develop and maintain open source projects related to cybersecurity.

EXPERIENCE

University professor

Universidad Central "Marta Abreu" de Las Villas | March 2022 - January 2024

- Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning researcher focused on agriculture.
- Professor of C++ programming using the Qt IDE and Framework.

Al model trainer

DataAnnotation Tech | February 2024 - May 2024

- Training and correction of AI models for chatbots using LLM.
- Training based on problem solving and typical development cases:
 - JavaScript
 - Python
 - C++

EDUCATION

Universidad Central "Marta Abreu" de Las Villas

Automatic Engineering | September 2019 - December 2022

Instituto Focán

Cybersecurity | May 2024 - Currently

CERTIFICATIONS

Full Stack Open

Universidad de Helsinki

Foundational C# with Microsoft

freeCodeCamp

PROJECTS

E-Comerce Web Page

- React.JS Node.JS MongoDB

Collaborative Calendar Web Page

- React.JS Node.JS MongoDB

Intelligent irrigation system

- Python
 Apache Spark

Hotel Manager

- C++ Qt

SKILLS

- JavaScriptTypeScript
- ExpressReactJs
- MongoDB

- NodeJS
- PostgreSQL
- Python
- C++

LANGUAGE

Spanish:

Native

English:

Intermediate | B1 +